My new book The Hidden Reality
takes on a grand question:
(Dr. Brian Greene:)Is our universe
the only universe?
(Dr. Brian Greene:)You see, there's a growing
belief among scientists like me
(Dr. Brian Greene:)that ours may only be one
among many universes
(Dr. Brian Greene:)populating a gigantic cosmos.
In The Hidden Reality,
I explore this possibility
(Dr. Brian Greene:)without presuming any knowledge
of mathematics or physics
(Dr. Brian Greene:)on the part of the reader.
(Sheldon:)Hysterical.
(Amy:)I'm glad you
talked me into this.
(Amy:)We work so hard, sometimes,
it's nice to goof off
(Amy:)and do something silly.
Agreed.
(Sheldon:)Wait till you hear how he dumbs down
Werner Heisenberg for the crowd.
(Sheldon:)You may actually believe
you're in a comedy club.
(Greene:)You can think about Heisenberg's
"uncertainty principle"
(Greene:)much like the special order menu
(Greene:)that you find in certain Chinese
restaurants, where you have
(Greene:)dishes in column A
and other dishes in column B,
(Greene:)and if you order the first dish
in column A,
(Greene:)you can't order the
corresponding dish in column B.
(Greene:)That's sort of like the
"uncertainly principle."
♪ Ba-dum-bump. ♪